What is that?
何だあれは?
Wow! It looks just like the town that was in virtual space!
すごいや！バーチャル空間にあった町にそっくりだ！
Professor, when will this town be finished?
博士、この町はいつ完成するの？
Yes, everything except the residential area
うん，居住区以外も
will be finished soon.
もうすぐ完成じゃろ。
They are testing the network right now,
ネットワークのテスト中らしいから、
if there are no problems, it'll be ready to go.
問題は無ければ、いよいよじゃんな。
Charu was implemented in part of the network, right?
ネットワークの一部にチャルちゃんが対応されたのよね。
Where? Where is she?
ねえ、どこ？どこにいるの？
Wow! Charu is everywhere!
うわー，チャルがいっぱいだ！
How many are there? Which one is the real Charu?
何人いるの？どれが本物のチャルなの？
I can multiply as much as I want, each one of them is the real me
私は何人にでもなれますし、どれも本物なんですよ。
You might say that I'm the entire town.
町全体が私と言ってもいいかもしれません。
Monkeys, go back to where you came from!
サルは大人しく住処に帰りなさい！
You should not have come here!
ここはお前たちが来るところではない！
Right now, our helicopter is flying over a
今、我々のヘリは空中に特殊現れた
massive battleship that has suddenly appeared in the sky.
巨大戦艦の上を飛んでいます。
There seems to be someone on what looks like the deck of the battleship.
巨大戦艦のデッキらしき部分の上には誰かいるようです。
It's a…monkey, it's an actual monkey!
…あれは…サル，なんとサルです！
There's a monkey on top of the battleship!
巨大な空中戦間の上にサルがいます！
Monkeys and other creatures standing there.
サルと追われる生物が複数立っています。
There are no signs of humans at all.
人の姿は全く確認できません。
Is this battleship crewed entirely by monkeys?
この戦艦の乗組は全員サルなのでしょうか？
Many monkeys have already started
すでに多数のサルの街に現れ，
attacking the city.
攻撃をしています。
Th-That's...?
あ、あれは…？
Wha,What is that!?
お、何だこれは！？
I'm..I'm on an island vacation right now!!
俺は..俺は今バカンスでこの島に来ているんだぞ！！
Who the hell is that!?
そいつは誰だ！？
What the hell are you doing?
お前ら何やってんだ！
Don't fall for it! That guy's a fake!
騙されるな、そいつは偽物だ！！
I'm right here!!
俺はここだ！！
Have you contacted them yet?
あいつらに連絡は取れたのか！？
What??
何！？
No one believes I'm the real one!?
誰も俺様が本物だと信じないだと！？
I'm so useless!!
俺は情けないぞ！！
Hmm....In that case, I'll go myself to expose
いいえええ....こんなった、偽物野郎を
I'm going to make those stupid monkeys who can't
告げに親分でやろう俺様の
Are you guys ready?
準備はできたか？お前ら！